in these uncertain times we can fall ill
on any day of the year just like a mask
that protects us from the harsh
environment similarly a group health
insurance plan provides cover against a
long list of expensive medical bills
group health insurance coverage is a
type of insurance plan that covers a
group of people who belong to the same
organization a health insurance is no
longer a benefit it's a necessity with a
group health insurance plan you can
create the best working space for your
employees providing them with a medical
cover that gives them a peace of mind
and shows them that you really care for
them and thus your employees remain ever
healthy resulting in improved
productivity a group health insurance
enables you to provide coverage to the
employees and their families at a much
lower cost it also covers pre-existing
conditions like heart disease diabetes
Etc from the Inception of the policy
add-on benefits such as maternity cover
can also be included in your group
health insurance plan you can walk up to
your insurer Network hospital and Avail
cashless treatment all necessary pre
post and inpatient hospitalization
charges are now fully covered under your
group health plan at the end of the day
an apple a day might not be enough to
keep the doctor awake
but we at Plum Insurance sure have you
covered